{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474175845","data":{"timestamp":" 947474175845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 45829003-78c0-4227-800f-c2e2e1745165"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" mpwa_mpwa_ikiwa_mbawa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474182459","data":{"timestamp":" 947474182459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 45829003-78c0-4227-800f-c2e2e1745165"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ziwa_ziwa_nilikuwa_itakuwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474189085","data":{"timestamp":" 947474189084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 45829003-78c0-4227-800f-c2e2e1745165"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_lililokuwa_zilikuwa_alishindwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474195731","data":{"timestamp":" 947474195731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 45829003-78c0-4227-800f-c2e2e1745165"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" palikuwa_palikuwa_njiwa_imefungwa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474202390","data":{"timestamp":" 947474202389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 45829003-78c0-4227-800f-c2e2e1745165"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" yalikuwa_yalikuwa_maziwa_lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474209027","data":{"timestamp":" 947474209026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 45829003-78c0-4227-800f-c2e2e1745165"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hewa_hewa_ingawa_nilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474215677","data":{"timestamp":" 947474215676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 45829003-78c0-4227-800f-c2e2e1745165"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" alijawa_huwa_alijawa_alipewa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474222301","data":{"timestamp":" 947474222300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 45829003-78c0-4227-800f-c2e2e1745165"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" mpendwa_mkubwa_palikuwa_mpendwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474228917","data":{"timestamp":" 947474228917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 45829003-78c0-4227-800f-c2e2e1745165"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" lilikuwa_akiwa_akawa_lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474235557","data":{"timestamp":" 947474235556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 45829003-78c0-4227-800f-c2e2e1745165"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" makubwa_alikunywa_makubwa_machungwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474243006","data":{"timestamp":" 947474243006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 45829003-78c0-4227-800f-c2e2e1745165"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" makubwa_alikunywa_makubwa_machungwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474255096","data":{"timestamp":" 947474255096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 45829003-78c0-4227-800f-c2e2e1745165"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" makubwa_alikunywa_makubwa_machungwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474271074","data":{"timestamp":" 947474271074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lililokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LILILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474274351","data":{"timestamp":" 947474274351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lililokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LILILOKUWA"," userResponse":" START_LILILOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474276061","data":{"timestamp":" 947474276060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lililokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LILILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474277673","data":{"timestamp":" 947474277673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" ZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474280228","data":{"timestamp":" 947474280228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" ZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474281828","data":{"timestamp":" 947474281828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hapakuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474285807","data":{"timestamp":" 947474285807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hapakuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474287405","data":{"timestamp":" 947474287404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" machungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHUNGWA"," userResponse":" MACHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474290336","data":{"timestamp":" 947474290336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" machungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MACHUNGWA"," userResponse":" START_MACHUNGWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474292765","data":{"timestamp":" 947474292765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" machungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHUNGWA"," userResponse":" MACHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474294380","data":{"timestamp":" 947474294379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMWA"," userResponse":" UMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474297439","data":{"timestamp":" 947474297439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMWA"," userResponse":" UMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474299028","data":{"timestamp":" 947474299027"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imefungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEFUNGWA"," userResponse":" IMEFUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474301729","data":{"timestamp":" 947474301729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imefungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" IMEFUNGWA"," userResponse":" START_IMEFUNGWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474304272","data":{"timestamp":" 947474304271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imefungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEFUNGWA"," userResponse":" IMEFUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474305877","data":{"timestamp":" 947474305876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliitwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" ALIITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474309135","data":{"timestamp":" 947474309134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliitwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" ALIITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474310745","data":{"timestamp":" 947474310744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hewa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEWA"," userResponse":" HEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474313106","data":{"timestamp":" 947474313106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hewa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEWA"," userResponse":" HEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474314721","data":{"timestamp":" 947474314720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukiwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIWA"," userResponse":" UKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474320907","data":{"timestamp":" 947474320906"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukiwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474322527","data":{"timestamp":" 947474322526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpendwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" MPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474325073","data":{"timestamp":" 947474325072"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpendwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" MPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474327097","data":{"timestamp":" 947474327096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mpendwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474327182","data":{"timestamp":" 947474327182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" faaa789c-4654-48f5-b19d-a3344928435c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpendwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" MPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474341782","data":{"timestamp":" 947474341782"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" walikuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_WALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474343617","data":{"timestamp":" 947474343616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" walikuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474344693","data":{"timestamp":" 947474344693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" walikuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474349757","data":{"timestamp":" 947474349756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anaitwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" START_ANAITWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474353015","data":{"timestamp":" 947474353015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anaitwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474354077","data":{"timestamp":" 947474354076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anaitwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474357661","data":{"timestamp":" 947474357661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akaagwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAAGWA"," userResponse":" AKAAGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474358717","data":{"timestamp":" 947474358717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akaagwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAAGWA"," userResponse":" AKAAGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474363114","data":{"timestamp":" 947474363114"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nilipokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474364170","data":{"timestamp":" 947474364169"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nilipokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474370972","data":{"timestamp":" 947474370972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474372046","data":{"timestamp":" 947474372045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474377136","data":{"timestamp":" 947474377135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akiwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474378204","data":{"timestamp":" 947474378203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akiwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474382555","data":{"timestamp":" 947474382554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hawa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474383607","data":{"timestamp":" 947474383606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hawa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474389258","data":{"timestamp":" 947474389258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" machungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MACHUNGWA"," userResponse":" START_MACHUNGWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474391211","data":{"timestamp":" 947474391210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" machungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHUNGWA"," userResponse":" MACHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474392293","data":{"timestamp":" 947474392292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" machungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHUNGWA"," userResponse":" MACHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474397607","data":{"timestamp":" 947474397607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliyekuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474398672","data":{"timestamp":" 947474398671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliyekuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474403746","data":{"timestamp":" 947474403746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" namukhaywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAMUKHAYWA"," userResponse":" START_NAMUKHAYWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474408312","data":{"timestamp":" 947474408312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" namukhaywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMUKHAYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474409368","data":{"timestamp":" 947474409367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" namukhaywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMUKHAYWA"," userResponse":" NAMUKHAYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474411325","data":{"timestamp":" 947474411324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" namukhaywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474411476","data":{"timestamp":" 947474411476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" f2e79d35-47c2-4e97-9603-94c6623b819f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.wa.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" namukhaywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMUKHAYWA"," userResponse":" NAMUKHAYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474440209","data":{"timestamp":" 947474440209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474442367","data":{"timestamp":" 947474442366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474451061","data":{"timestamp":" 947474451061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474454144","data":{"timestamp":" 947474454144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474462838","data":{"timestamp":" 947474462838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474466115","data":{"timestamp":" 947474466115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474474300","data":{"timestamp":" 947474474300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474486214","data":{"timestamp":" 947474486214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474495899","data":{"timestamp":" 947474495899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474498234","data":{"timestamp":" 947474498234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474507326","data":{"timestamp":" 947474507326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474514625","data":{"timestamp":" 947474514625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474516450","data":{"timestamp":" 947474516450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474529812","data":{"timestamp":" 947474529812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474539603","data":{"timestamp":" 947474539603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474549881","data":{"timestamp":" 947474549881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474555209","data":{"timestamp":" 947474555209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474563680","data":{"timestamp":" 947474563680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474582228","data":{"timestamp":" 947474582228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474589203","data":{"timestamp":" 947474589203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474593301","data":{"timestamp":" 947474593301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474603324","data":{"timestamp":" 947474603324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474605582","data":{"timestamp":" 947474605582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474614059","data":{"timestamp":" 947474614059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474616203","data":{"timestamp":" 947474616202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474629515","data":{"timestamp":" 947474629514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b50ecbe5-9520-43c4-aea7-81378b3d1c32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474662698","data":{"timestamp":" 947474662698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474664429","data":{"timestamp":" 947474664428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474673973","data":{"timestamp":" 947474673973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474681465","data":{"timestamp":" 947474681465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474685875","data":{"timestamp":" 947474685875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474697499","data":{"timestamp":" 947474697499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474701218","data":{"timestamp":" 947474701218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474710531","data":{"timestamp":" 947474710531"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474714327","data":{"timestamp":" 947474714327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474740486","data":{"timestamp":" 947474740486"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474751089","data":{"timestamp":" 947474751089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474753331","data":{"timestamp":" 947474753331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474761780","data":{"timestamp":" 947474761780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474763777","data":{"timestamp":" 947474763777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474773030","data":{"timestamp":" 947474773030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474775241","data":{"timestamp":" 947474775241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474791224","data":{"timestamp":" 947474791224"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474793308","data":{"timestamp":" 947474793308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474804455","data":{"timestamp":" 947474804455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474806942","data":{"timestamp":" 947474806942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474819642","data":{"timestamp":" 947474819642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474823514","data":{"timestamp":" 947474823514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474831967","data":{"timestamp":" 947474831967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474841530","data":{"timestamp":" 947474841530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474856553","data":{"timestamp":" 947474856551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef3f17ff-a168-4190-8eb7-585eebeffffa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.we.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474868978","data":{"timestamp":" 947474868978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 368bb64c-3125-416a-9fe3-d9055258f682"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.we.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWE"," userResponse":" WAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.we.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474871989","data":{"timestamp":" 947474871988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 368bb64c-3125-416a-9fe3-d9055258f682"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.we.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAWE"," userResponse":" YAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.we.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474875037","data":{"timestamp":" 947474875036"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 368bb64c-3125-416a-9fe3-d9055258f682"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.we.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" magozwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGOZWE"," userResponse":" MAGOZWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.we.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474878269","data":{"timestamp":" 947474878269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 368bb64c-3125-416a-9fe3-d9055258f682"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.we.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAWE"," userResponse":" MWANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.we.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474881482","data":{"timestamp":" 947474881481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 368bb64c-3125-416a-9fe3-d9055258f682"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.we.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mayowe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.we.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474884661","data":{"timestamp":" 947474884660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 368bb64c-3125-416a-9fe3-d9055258f682"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.we.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWE"," userResponse":" ZIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.we.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474887540","data":{"timestamp":" 947474887539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 368bb64c-3125-416a-9fe3-d9055258f682"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.we.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yowe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOWE"," userResponse":" YOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.we.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474890454","data":{"timestamp":" 947474890453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 368bb64c-3125-416a-9fe3-d9055258f682"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.we.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWE"," userResponse":" MAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.we.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474893353","data":{"timestamp":" 947474893351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 368bb64c-3125-416a-9fe3-d9055258f682"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.we.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wenyewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYEWE"," userResponse":" WENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.we.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474896387","data":{"timestamp":" 947474896386"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 368bb64c-3125-416a-9fe3-d9055258f682"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.we.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGWE"," userResponse":" NGWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.we.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474899576","data":{"timestamp":" 947474899575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 368bb64c-3125-416a-9fe3-d9055258f682"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.we.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ngwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474899687","data":{"timestamp":" 947474899687"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 368bb64c-3125-416a-9fe3-d9055258f682"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.we.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGWE"," userResponse":" NGWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474931843","data":{"timestamp":" 947474931843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 46b1a682-f579-477e-ace0-ad82e924e9e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mawe_mawe-tawi-wapi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mawe"," userResponse":" mawe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474940061","data":{"timestamp":" 947474940061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 46b1a682-f579-477e-ace0-ad82e924e9e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jiwe_jiwe-hebu-ndoo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jiwe"," userResponse":" jiwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474948833","data":{"timestamp":" 947474948833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 46b1a682-f579-477e-ace0-ad82e924e9e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_yawe_yawe-umwa-wivu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" yawe"," userResponse":" yawe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474958228","data":{"timestamp":" 947474958228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 46b1a682-f579-477e-ace0-ad82e924e9e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_yowe_yowe-nasi-wiki"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" yowe"," userResponse":" yowe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474967189","data":{"timestamp":" 947474967189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 46b1a682-f579-477e-ace0-ad82e924e9e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wewe_wewe-safi-hawa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wewe"," userResponse":" hawa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474976457","data":{"timestamp":" 947474976456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 46b1a682-f579-477e-ace0-ad82e924e9e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wewe_wewe-safi-hawa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wewe"," userResponse":" wewe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474985196","data":{"timestamp":" 947474985195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 46b1a682-f579-477e-ace0-ad82e924e9e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mawe_hiki-mawe-jike"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mawe"," userResponse":" mawe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474993959","data":{"timestamp":" 947474993959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 46b1a682-f579-477e-ace0-ad82e924e9e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wewe_duni-damu-wewe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wewe"," userResponse":" wewe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475002613","data":{"timestamp":" 947475002613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 46b1a682-f579-477e-ace0-ad82e924e9e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kiwe_saba-kiwe-naro"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kiwe"," userResponse":" kiwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475012247","data":{"timestamp":" 947475012247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 46b1a682-f579-477e-ace0-ad82e924e9e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_niwe_ombe-humu-niwe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" niwe"," userResponse":" niwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475021609","data":{"timestamp":" 947475021609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 46b1a682-f579-477e-ace0-ad82e924e9e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wewe_kati-jina-wewe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wewe"," userResponse":" wewe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475027355","data":{"timestamp":" 947475027354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 46b1a682-f579-477e-ace0-ad82e924e9e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_wewe_kati-jina-wewe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475054840","data":{"timestamp":" 947475054839"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b59e8524-ab62-4d32-9194-1a4bb627d5f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ziwe_mayowe_maharagwe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475061513","data":{"timestamp":" 947475061513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b59e8524-ab62-4d32-9194-1a4bb627d5f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" jiwe_usichukuwe_mkewe_jiwe"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475068143","data":{"timestamp":" 947475068141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b59e8524-ab62-4d32-9194-1a4bb627d5f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" usiwe_niwe_mkongwe_usiwe"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475074803","data":{"timestamp":" 947475074803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b59e8524-ab62-4d32-9194-1a4bb627d5f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wewe_mumewe_wewe_usiwe"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475081464","data":{"timestamp":" 947475081464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b59e8524-ab62-4d32-9194-1a4bb627d5f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" usiwe_wenyewe_ngwe_usiwe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475088078","data":{"timestamp":" 947475088078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b59e8524-ab62-4d32-9194-1a4bb627d5f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" mwanawe_niwe_mwanawe_magozwe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475095585","data":{"timestamp":" 947475095585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b59e8524-ab62-4d32-9194-1a4bb627d5f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" mwanawe_niwe_mwanawe_magozwe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475102223","data":{"timestamp":" 947475102223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b59e8524-ab62-4d32-9194-1a4bb627d5f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" mawe_mawe_mkwewe_jiwe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475108854","data":{"timestamp":" 947475108853"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b59e8524-ab62-4d32-9194-1a4bb627d5f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wenyewe_mkewe_wenyewe_mumewe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475116328","data":{"timestamp":" 947475116328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b59e8524-ab62-4d32-9194-1a4bb627d5f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wenyewe_mkewe_wenyewe_mumewe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475122994","data":{"timestamp":" 947475122994"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b59e8524-ab62-4d32-9194-1a4bb627d5f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" jiwe_jiwe_ngwe_mkongwe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475129644","data":{"timestamp":" 947475129644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b59e8524-ab62-4d32-9194-1a4bb627d5f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mawe_jiwe_mwishowe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475141708","data":{"timestamp":" 947475141707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b59e8524-ab62-4d32-9194-1a4bb627d5f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_mawe_jiwe_mwishowe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475162434","data":{"timestamp":" 947475162434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" add4833b-d938-4280-8152-b91150e82334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_niwe_debe-ubao-niwe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" niwe"," userResponse":" niwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475183239","data":{"timestamp":" 947475183239"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" add4833b-d938-4280-8152-b91150e82334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nawe_hana-nawe-kima"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nawe"," userResponse":" nawe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475192270","data":{"timestamp":" 947475192270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" add4833b-d938-4280-8152-b91150e82334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jiwe_waje-ebei-jiwe"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jiwe"," userResponse":" jiwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475201890","data":{"timestamp":" 947475201890"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" add4833b-d938-4280-8152-b91150e82334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ziwe_ziwe-eupe-kima"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ziwe"," userResponse":" ziwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475212678","data":{"timestamp":" 947475212678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" add4833b-d938-4280-8152-b91150e82334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jiwe_waua-bali-jiwe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jiwe"," userResponse":" jiwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475222015","data":{"timestamp":" 947475222015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" add4833b-d938-4280-8152-b91150e82334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kiwe_kiwe-nchi-huyu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kiwe"," userResponse":" kiwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475230586","data":{"timestamp":" 947475230586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" add4833b-d938-4280-8152-b91150e82334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_yawe_kuni-yawe-sisa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" yawe"," userResponse":" yawe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475240444","data":{"timestamp":" 947475240444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" add4833b-d938-4280-8152-b91150e82334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tuwe_tuwe-titi-hoho"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tuwe"," userResponse":" tuwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475249016","data":{"timestamp":" 947475249016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" add4833b-d938-4280-8152-b91150e82334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kiwe_kiwe-ruka-zile"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kiwe"," userResponse":" kiwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475258007","data":{"timestamp":" 947475258007"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" add4833b-d938-4280-8152-b91150e82334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tuwe_hapo-tuwe-lele"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tuwe"," userResponse":" tuwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475263779","data":{"timestamp":" 947475263779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" add4833b-d938-4280-8152-b91150e82334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_tuwe_hapo-tuwe-lele"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475279689","data":{"timestamp":" 947475279688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIWE"," userResponse":" USIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475283870","data":{"timestamp":" 947475283869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIWE"," userResponse":" USIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475285465","data":{"timestamp":" 947475285464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475288178","data":{"timestamp":" 947475288177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475289792","data":{"timestamp":" 947475289790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wanawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWE"," userResponse":" WANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475292858","data":{"timestamp":" 947475292857"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wanawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWE"," userResponse":" WANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475294457","data":{"timestamp":" 947475294456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkwewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKWEWE"," userResponse":" MKWEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475297256","data":{"timestamp":" 947475297255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkwewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKWEWE"," userResponse":" MKWEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475298854","data":{"timestamp":" 947475298853"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIWE"," userResponse":" KIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475301240","data":{"timestamp":" 947475301240"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIWE"," userResponse":" KIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475302842","data":{"timestamp":" 947475302842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkongwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONGWE"," userResponse":" MKONGWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475306026","data":{"timestamp":" 947475306025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkongwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONGWE"," userResponse":" MKONGWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475307636","data":{"timestamp":" 947475307635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwenyewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475310529","data":{"timestamp":" 947475310528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwenyewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475312127","data":{"timestamp":" 947475312127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" NAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475315213","data":{"timestamp":" 947475315213"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" NAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475316804","data":{"timestamp":" 947475316803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yowe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOWE"," userResponse":" YOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475323410","data":{"timestamp":" 947475323410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yowe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOWE"," userResponse":" YOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475325033","data":{"timestamp":" 947475325032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wenyewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYEWE"," userResponse":" WENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475327951","data":{"timestamp":" 947475327950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wenyewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYEWE"," userResponse":" WENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475329985","data":{"timestamp":" 947475329984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" wenyewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475330097","data":{"timestamp":" 947475330097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c276dc91-8ef5-49c5-99e1-c36b949fbf1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wenyewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYEWE"," userResponse":" WENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475353353","data":{"timestamp":" 947475353352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWE"," userResponse":" WAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475354408","data":{"timestamp":" 947475354407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWE"," userResponse":" WAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475358670","data":{"timestamp":" 947475358669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475359731","data":{"timestamp":" 947475359730"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475364155","data":{"timestamp":" 947475364155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" NAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475365211","data":{"timestamp":" 947475365210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" NAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475371653","data":{"timestamp":" 947475371652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWE"," userResponse":" ZIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475372725","data":{"timestamp":" 947475372725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWE"," userResponse":" ZIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475376910","data":{"timestamp":" 947475376909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWE"," userResponse":" MAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475377973","data":{"timestamp":" 947475377972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWE"," userResponse":" MAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475383269","data":{"timestamp":" 947475383268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yowe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOWE"," userResponse":" YOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475384347","data":{"timestamp":" 947475384346"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yowe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOWE"," userResponse":" YOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475389456","data":{"timestamp":" 947475389455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nguruwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475390514","data":{"timestamp":" 947475390514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nguruwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475393358","data":{"timestamp":" 947475393358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kamwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMWE"," userResponse":" KAMWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475394418","data":{"timestamp":" 947475394418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kamwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMWE"," userResponse":" KAMWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475398235","data":{"timestamp":" 947475398234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwishowe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHOWE"," userResponse":" MWISHOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475399297","data":{"timestamp":" 947475399296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwishowe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHOWE"," userResponse":" MWISHOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475403019","data":{"timestamp":" 947475403019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wanawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWE"," userResponse":" START_WANAWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475404660","data":{"timestamp":" 947475404659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wanawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWE"," userResponse":" WANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475405713","data":{"timestamp":" 947475405712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wanawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWE"," userResponse":" WANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475409364","data":{"timestamp":" 947475409363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" wanawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475409463","data":{"timestamp":" 947475409463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b0bb1aca-1061-4648-8349-246a4c04b714"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.we.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wanawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWE"," userResponse":" WANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475441357","data":{"timestamp":" 947475441356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475443395","data":{"timestamp":" 947475443395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475460266","data":{"timestamp":" 947475460266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475474603","data":{"timestamp":" 947475474603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475481169","data":{"timestamp":" 947475481169"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475495881","data":{"timestamp":" 947475495880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475498400","data":{"timestamp":" 947475498400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475507004","data":{"timestamp":" 947475507004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475509767","data":{"timestamp":" 947475509766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475518657","data":{"timestamp":" 947475518656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475521098","data":{"timestamp":" 947475521098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475527412","data":{"timestamp":" 947475527412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475538717","data":{"timestamp":" 947475538717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475540743","data":{"timestamp":" 947475540743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475556506","data":{"timestamp":" 947475556506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475558744","data":{"timestamp":" 947475558744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475582198","data":{"timestamp":" 947475582198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475590057","data":{"timestamp":" 947475590057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475597902","data":{"timestamp":" 947475597902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475600874","data":{"timestamp":" 947475600874"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475611653","data":{"timestamp":" 947475611653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475618139","data":{"timestamp":" 947475618139"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475619968","data":{"timestamp":" 947475619968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475625663","data":{"timestamp":" 947475625662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475637082","data":{"timestamp":" 947475637082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475639607","data":{"timestamp":" 947475639606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475652935","data":{"timestamp":" 947475652933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 13f4f06b-50e1-43a7-8a03-f0d75c205a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.all.noShow.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475683210","data":{"timestamp":" 947475683210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 10375f2b-ed9f-4719-bb71-0a3f42e9aa6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.all.noShow.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nani_kwao-dawa-nani"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" nani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.all.noShow.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475691923","data":{"timestamp":" 947475691923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 10375f2b-ed9f-4719-bb71-0a3f42e9aa6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.all.noShow.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuua_kuua-lini-koko"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuua"," userResponse":" kuua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.all.noShow.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475700926","data":{"timestamp":" 947475700926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 10375f2b-ed9f-4719-bb71-0a3f42e9aa6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.all.noShow.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nalo_nalo-omba-nawe"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nalo"," userResponse":" nalo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.all.noShow.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475710679","data":{"timestamp":" 947475710679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 10375f2b-ed9f-4719-bb71-0a3f42e9aa6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.all.noShow.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wake_yako-sawa-wake"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wake"," userResponse":" wake"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.all.noShow.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475727977","data":{"timestamp":" 947475727976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 10375f2b-ed9f-4719-bb71-0a3f42e9aa6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.all.noShow.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nayo_jiko-nayo-papa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nayo"," userResponse":" jiko"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.all.noShow.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475738007","data":{"timestamp":" 947475738007"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 10375f2b-ed9f-4719-bb71-0a3f42e9aa6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.all.noShow.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nayo_jiko-nayo-papa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nayo"," userResponse":" nayo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.all.noShow.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475747175","data":{"timestamp":" 947475747175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 10375f2b-ed9f-4719-bb71-0a3f42e9aa6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.all.noShow.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kule_vuta-kule-eupe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kule"," userResponse":" kule"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.all.noShow.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475760589","data":{"timestamp":" 947475760589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 10375f2b-ed9f-4719-bb71-0a3f42e9aa6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.all.noShow.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_waua_waua-hiyo-fupi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" waua"," userResponse":" waua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.all.noShow.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475772077","data":{"timestamp":" 947475772077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 10375f2b-ed9f-4719-bb71-0a3f42e9aa6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.all.noShow.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sita_papo-sita-haha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sita"," userResponse":" sita"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.all.noShow.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475781098","data":{"timestamp":" 947475781098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 10375f2b-ed9f-4719-bb71-0a3f42e9aa6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.all.noShow.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wawe_hapa-hula-wawe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wawe"," userResponse":" wawe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.all.noShow.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475791253","data":{"timestamp":" 947475791253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 10375f2b-ed9f-4719-bb71-0a3f42e9aa6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.all.noShow.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tatu_kule-tatu-vuta"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tatu"," userResponse":" tatu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.all.noShow.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475797053","data":{"timestamp":" 947475797051"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 10375f2b-ed9f-4719-bb71-0a3f42e9aa6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.all.noShow.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_tatu_kule-tatu-vuta"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475815417","data":{"timestamp":" 947475815417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" cc65d21c-64a1-4c21-ac98-df0475889137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngwe_mito-nchi-ngwe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngwe"," userResponse":" ngwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475825107","data":{"timestamp":" 947475825107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" cc65d21c-64a1-4c21-ac98-df0475889137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hili_geni-saba-hili"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hili"," userResponse":" hili"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475835140","data":{"timestamp":" 947475835139"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" cc65d21c-64a1-4c21-ac98-df0475889137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tisa_koti-tisa-saba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tisa"," userResponse":" tisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475844250","data":{"timestamp":" 947475844249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" cc65d21c-64a1-4c21-ac98-df0475889137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kiko_yowe-kiko-sifa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kiko"," userResponse":" kiko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475852959","data":{"timestamp":" 947475852959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" cc65d21c-64a1-4c21-ac98-df0475889137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bali_tuzo-bali-goso"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bali"," userResponse":" bali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475863169","data":{"timestamp":" 947475863169"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" cc65d21c-64a1-4c21-ac98-df0475889137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hawa_nazo-kasa-hawa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hawa"," userResponse":" hawa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475872782","data":{"timestamp":" 947475872782"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" cc65d21c-64a1-4c21-ac98-df0475889137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tuna_hula-tuna-pale"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tuna"," userResponse":" tuna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475881133","data":{"timestamp":" 947475881133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" cc65d21c-64a1-4c21-ac98-df0475889137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sana_sana-hema-nazo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sana"," userResponse":" sana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475890064","data":{"timestamp":" 947475890063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" cc65d21c-64a1-4c21-ac98-df0475889137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuna_goso-ziwa-kuna"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuna"," userResponse":" kuna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475897964","data":{"timestamp":" 947475897964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" cc65d21c-64a1-4c21-ac98-df0475889137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lima_lima-tope-hiki"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lima"," userResponse":" lima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475903744","data":{"timestamp":" 947475903742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" cc65d21c-64a1-4c21-ac98-df0475889137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_lima_lima-tope-hiki"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475921605","data":{"timestamp":" 947475921605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475922372","data":{"timestamp":" 947475922371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMOJA"," userResponse":" KIMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475923225","data":{"timestamp":" 947475923225"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475923933","data":{"timestamp":" 947475923932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475924157","data":{"timestamp":" 947475924157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475924839","data":{"timestamp":" 947475924839"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475925613","data":{"timestamp":" 947475925613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475932302","data":{"timestamp":" 947475932302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475935613","data":{"timestamp":" 947475935612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMOJA"," userResponse":" KIMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475935623","data":{"timestamp":" 947475935623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475937976","data":{"timestamp":" 947475937976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475939015","data":{"timestamp":" 947475939015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KIMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475940628","data":{"timestamp":" 947475940627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475941288","data":{"timestamp":" 947475941288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475942026","data":{"timestamp":" 947475942025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475942940","data":{"timestamp":" 947475942940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475943940","data":{"timestamp":" 947475943940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475946318","data":{"timestamp":" 947475946318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475946872","data":{"timestamp":" 947475946871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475947649","data":{"timestamp":" 947475947648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475947903","data":{"timestamp":" 947475947902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475948650","data":{"timestamp":" 947475948650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" MAJITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475950766","data":{"timestamp":" 947475950765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475951174","data":{"timestamp":" 947475951174"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475951782","data":{"timestamp":" 947475951781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475952840","data":{"timestamp":" 947475952840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475953380","data":{"timestamp":" 947475953380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" MAJITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475955585","data":{"timestamp":" 947475955584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475956416","data":{"timestamp":" 947475956416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475957233","data":{"timestamp":" 947475957233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALILIWA"," userResponse":" WALILIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475957418","data":{"timestamp":" 947475957418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475958187","data":{"timestamp":" 947475958186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" MAJITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475960037","data":{"timestamp":" 947475960037"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475960539","data":{"timestamp":" 947475960539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" START_WENGI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475961342","data":{"timestamp":" 947475961340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475962863","data":{"timestamp":" 947475962862"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475964303","data":{"timestamp":" 947475964302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALILIWA"," userResponse":" WALILIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475965229","data":{"timestamp":" 947475965229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475965345","data":{"timestamp":" 947475965345"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" MAJITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475968070","data":{"timestamp":" 947475968069"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EKENO"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475968926","data":{"timestamp":" 947475968925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONYWA"," userResponse":" ALIONYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475969116","data":{"timestamp":" 947475969115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475970056","data":{"timestamp":" 947475970056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475971120","data":{"timestamp":" 947475971119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIINGIE"," userResponse":" ASIINGIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475972108","data":{"timestamp":" 947475972108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475974247","data":{"timestamp":" 947475974246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EKENO"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475975550","data":{"timestamp":" 947475975549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONYWA"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475977354","data":{"timestamp":" 947475977354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONYWA"," userResponse":" ALIONYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475978251","data":{"timestamp":" 947475978251"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475978918","data":{"timestamp":" 947475978918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475979877","data":{"timestamp":" 947475979877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ASIINGIE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475980705","data":{"timestamp":" 947475980705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ASIINGIE"," userResponse":" START_ASIINGIE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475982613","data":{"timestamp":" 947475982613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIINGIE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475983992","data":{"timestamp":" 947475983992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475986405","data":{"timestamp":" 947475986405"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EKENO"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475987732","data":{"timestamp":" 947475987731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPUUZA"," userResponse":" ALIPUUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475988471","data":{"timestamp":" 947475988471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USHAURI"," userResponse":" USHAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475988686","data":{"timestamp":" 947475988686"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475989385","data":{"timestamp":" 947475989385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475991320","data":{"timestamp":" 947475991319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EKENO"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475993104","data":{"timestamp":" 947475993104"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPUUZA"," userResponse":" ALIPUUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475994239","data":{"timestamp":" 947475994239"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" USHAURI"," userResponse":" START_USHAURI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475996338","data":{"timestamp":" 947475996338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" USHAURI"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475998090","data":{"timestamp":" 947475998090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USHAURI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947475998767","data":{"timestamp":" 947475998766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476001452","data":{"timestamp":" 947476001452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476003778","data":{"timestamp":" 947476003777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476006119","data":{"timestamp":" 947476006118"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476006634","data":{"timestamp":" 947476006634"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476007487","data":{"timestamp":" 947476007486"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" AKAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476008481","data":{"timestamp":" 947476008481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476010482","data":{"timestamp":" 947476010482"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476010867","data":{"timestamp":" 947476010866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476011911","data":{"timestamp":" 947476011911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" START_AKAENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476012709","data":{"timestamp":" 947476012709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476014404","data":{"timestamp":" 947476014403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476015563","data":{"timestamp":" 947476015562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476017659","data":{"timestamp":" 947476017659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476020059","data":{"timestamp":" 947476020059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476021167","data":{"timestamp":" 947476021166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" ALIKUTANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476021393","data":{"timestamp":" 947476021392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476021967","data":{"timestamp":" 947476021967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476024751","data":{"timestamp":" 947476024750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476025256","data":{"timestamp":" 947476025256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" START_ALIKUTANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476026540","data":{"timestamp":" 947476026540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" ALIKUTANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476027644","data":{"timestamp":" 947476027644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476027840","data":{"timestamp":" 947476027840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476030815","data":{"timestamp":" 947476030815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPELEKA"," userResponse":" ALIMPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476031845","data":{"timestamp":" 947476031844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476031951","data":{"timestamp":" 947476031951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476032507","data":{"timestamp":" 947476032506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476035012","data":{"timestamp":" 947476035011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPELEKA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMPELEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476036536","data":{"timestamp":" 947476036535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPELEKA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMPELEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476038448","data":{"timestamp":" 947476038447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPELEKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476039703","data":{"timestamp":" 947476039703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476040419","data":{"timestamp":" 947476040419"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476040725","data":{"timestamp":" 947476040724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" START_MSITU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476044238","data":{"timestamp":" 947476044238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476047082","data":{"timestamp":" 947476047081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVAMIWA"," userResponse":" ALIVAMIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476047251","data":{"timestamp":" 947476047250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476048009","data":{"timestamp":" 947476048008"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" MAJITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476049029","data":{"timestamp":" 947476049029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMLA"," userResponse":" WAKAMLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476051215","data":{"timestamp":" 947476051215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVAMIWA"," userResponse":" ALIVAMIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476052445","data":{"timestamp":" 947476052444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476053037","data":{"timestamp":" 947476053037"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" MAJITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476054442","data":{"timestamp":" 947476054442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMLA"," userResponse":" WAKAMLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476056940","data":{"timestamp":" 947476056940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" WENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476057735","data":{"timestamp":" 947476057734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476058892","data":{"timestamp":" 947476058891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUMTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476060974","data":{"timestamp":" 947476060974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" WENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476061381","data":{"timestamp":" 947476061381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" START_WALIENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476063213","data":{"timestamp":" 947476063212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476065020","data":{"timestamp":" 947476065020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUMTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476067472","data":{"timestamp":" 947476067471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476068135","data":{"timestamp":" 947476068134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476069583","data":{"timestamp":" 947476069582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEKEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWAELEKEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476070101","data":{"timestamp":" 947476070100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476071168","data":{"timestamp":" 947476071167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EKENO"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476072042","data":{"timestamp":" 947476072041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINGIA"," userResponse":" ALIINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476073011","data":{"timestamp":" 947476073011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476074761","data":{"timestamp":" 947476074761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" START_JIRANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476076335","data":{"timestamp":" 947476076334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476077458","data":{"timestamp":" 947476077458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476078831","data":{"timestamp":" 947476078831"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEKEZA"," userResponse":" START_ALIWAELEKEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476080742","data":{"timestamp":" 947476080742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEKEZA"," userResponse":" START_ALIWAELEKEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476082793","data":{"timestamp":" 947476082793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEKEZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476083873","data":{"timestamp":" 947476083872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476085363","data":{"timestamp":" 947476085362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EKENO"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476086963","data":{"timestamp":" 947476086962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINGIA"," userResponse":" ALIINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476088597","data":{"timestamp":" 947476088597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476091571","data":{"timestamp":" 947476091570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMINI"," userResponse":" WALIAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476092199","data":{"timestamp":" 947476092199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476092906","data":{"timestamp":" 947476092905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELIWA"," userResponse":" AMELIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476093110","data":{"timestamp":" 947476093109"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476093712","data":{"timestamp":" 947476093711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476095526","data":{"timestamp":" 947476095526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMINI"," userResponse":" START_WALIAMINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476096919","data":{"timestamp":" 947476096919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMINI"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476099021","data":{"timestamp":" 947476099021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMINI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476100108","data":{"timestamp":" 947476100108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" AMELIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476101715","data":{"timestamp":" 947476101715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476104380","data":{"timestamp":" 947476104379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMELIWA"," userResponse":" START_AMELIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476106024","data":{"timestamp":" 947476106023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELIWA"," userResponse":" AMELIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476106405","data":{"timestamp":" 947476106405"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476107426","data":{"timestamp":" 947476107425"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476109438","data":{"timestamp":" 947476109436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476109551","data":{"timestamp":" 947476109551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 06a7a90a-7e13-474c-bda0-7f4e4562732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476122324","data":{"timestamp":" 947476122324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476132928","data":{"timestamp":" 947476132927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476135115","data":{"timestamp":" 947476135115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476136420","data":{"timestamp":" 947476136420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476137710","data":{"timestamp":" 947476137710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476138721","data":{"timestamp":" 947476138721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476139730","data":{"timestamp":" 947476139729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476140264","data":{"timestamp":" 947476140264"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476142219","data":{"timestamp":" 947476142218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476142987","data":{"timestamp":" 947476142986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMOJA"," userResponse":" KIMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476143843","data":{"timestamp":" 947476143843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476144554","data":{"timestamp":" 947476144554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476144781","data":{"timestamp":" 947476144780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476145454","data":{"timestamp":" 947476145453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476146221","data":{"timestamp":" 947476146221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476148909","data":{"timestamp":" 947476148909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476149313","data":{"timestamp":" 947476149312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476150410","data":{"timestamp":" 947476150410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476151546","data":{"timestamp":" 947476151545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476153010","data":{"timestamp":" 947476153010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476155237","data":{"timestamp":" 947476155237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" START_MAJITU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476156724","data":{"timestamp":" 947476156724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" MAJITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476158571","data":{"timestamp":" 947476158571"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476159127","data":{"timestamp":" 947476159126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476159905","data":{"timestamp":" 947476159904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476160169","data":{"timestamp":" 947476160168"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476160916","data":{"timestamp":" 947476160915"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" MAJITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476164704","data":{"timestamp":" 947476164704"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476165480","data":{"timestamp":" 947476165480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476165923","data":{"timestamp":" 947476165923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALILIWA"," userResponse":" MAJITU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476167360","data":{"timestamp":" 947476167360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALILIWA"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476169089","data":{"timestamp":" 947476169088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALILIWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476170460","data":{"timestamp":" 947476170459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" WALILIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476172069","data":{"timestamp":" 947476172068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476172542","data":{"timestamp":" 947476172541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" MAJITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476174186","data":{"timestamp":" 947476174185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476175028","data":{"timestamp":" 947476175027"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476175841","data":{"timestamp":" 947476175840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALILIWA"," userResponse":" WALILIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476176024","data":{"timestamp":" 947476176022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476176791","data":{"timestamp":" 947476176791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" MAJITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476180681","data":{"timestamp":" 947476180681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EKENO"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476182235","data":{"timestamp":" 947476182235"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONYWA"," userResponse":" ALIONYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476182238","data":{"timestamp":" 947476182238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476182364","data":{"timestamp":" 947476182364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476184266","data":{"timestamp":" 947476184266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" START_WAZAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476186154","data":{"timestamp":" 947476186153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476187557","data":{"timestamp":" 947476187556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ASIINGIE"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476189782","data":{"timestamp":" 947476189782"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIINGIE"," userResponse":" ASIINGIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476190979","data":{"timestamp":" 947476190978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476193120","data":{"timestamp":" 947476193120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EKENO"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476193966","data":{"timestamp":" 947476193965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONYWA"," userResponse":" ALIONYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476194161","data":{"timestamp":" 947476194160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476195104","data":{"timestamp":" 947476195103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476196150","data":{"timestamp":" 947476196149"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIINGIE"," userResponse":" ASIINGIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476197141","data":{"timestamp":" 947476197141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476200595","data":{"timestamp":" 947476200595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EKENO"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476202232","data":{"timestamp":" 947476202232"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPUUZA"," userResponse":" ALIPUUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476203210","data":{"timestamp":" 947476203210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" USHAURI"," userResponse":" START_USHAURI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476204867","data":{"timestamp":" 947476204866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USHAURI"," userResponse":" USHAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476205960","data":{"timestamp":" 947476205960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476206470","data":{"timestamp":" 947476206470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476208334","data":{"timestamp":" 947476208333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EKENO"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476209662","data":{"timestamp":" 947476209661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPUUZA"," userResponse":" ALIPUUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476210397","data":{"timestamp":" 947476210397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USHAURI"," userResponse":" USHAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476210614","data":{"timestamp":" 947476210613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476211312","data":{"timestamp":" 947476211311"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476214852","data":{"timestamp":" 947476214852"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" AKAENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476215743","data":{"timestamp":" 947476215743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476217930","data":{"timestamp":" 947476217930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476220035","data":{"timestamp":" 947476220034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" START_AKAENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476221378","data":{"timestamp":" 947476221377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" AKAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476222302","data":{"timestamp":" 947476222301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" AKAENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476223290","data":{"timestamp":" 947476223289"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476225100","data":{"timestamp":" 947476225100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476225614","data":{"timestamp":" 947476225613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476226477","data":{"timestamp":" 947476226476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" AKAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476227469","data":{"timestamp":" 947476227468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476233370","data":{"timestamp":" 947476233369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476234815","data":{"timestamp":" 947476234814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476235959","data":{"timestamp":" 947476235958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" ALIKUTANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476237155","data":{"timestamp":" 947476237154"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476238678","data":{"timestamp":" 947476238677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476240511","data":{"timestamp":" 947476240510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476241621","data":{"timestamp":" 947476241620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" ALIKUTANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476241846","data":{"timestamp":" 947476241845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476242424","data":{"timestamp":" 947476242423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476246697","data":{"timestamp":" 947476246697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPELEKA"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476248611","data":{"timestamp":" 947476248610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPELEKA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMPELEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476250564","data":{"timestamp":" 947476250563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPELEKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476251965","data":{"timestamp":" 947476251965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" START_KATIKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476252759","data":{"timestamp":" 947476252759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" START_KATIKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476254344","data":{"timestamp":" 947476254343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476254707","data":{"timestamp":" 947476254706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476256128","data":{"timestamp":" 947476256127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" START_MSITU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476258232","data":{"timestamp":" 947476258232"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476260690","data":{"timestamp":" 947476260689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPELEKA"," userResponse":" ALIMPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476261717","data":{"timestamp":" 947476261716"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476261824","data":{"timestamp":" 947476261824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476262389","data":{"timestamp":" 947476262388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476266822","data":{"timestamp":" 947476266822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVAMIWA"," userResponse":" START_MAJITU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476267749","data":{"timestamp":" 947476267749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVAMIWA"," userResponse":" ALIVAMIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476268644","data":{"timestamp":" 947476268644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476269347","data":{"timestamp":" 947476269347"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" MAJITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476270752","data":{"timestamp":" 947476270752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMLA"," userResponse":" WAKAMLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476273076","data":{"timestamp":" 947476273075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVAMIWA"," userResponse":" ALIVAMIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476273247","data":{"timestamp":" 947476273246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476274003","data":{"timestamp":" 947476274002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" MAJITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476275018","data":{"timestamp":" 947476275018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMLA"," userResponse":" WAKAMLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476279209","data":{"timestamp":" 947476279208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" START_WENZAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476281062","data":{"timestamp":" 947476281061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" WENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476282459","data":{"timestamp":" 947476282459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" START_WALIENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476284494","data":{"timestamp":" 947476284494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476286141","data":{"timestamp":" 947476286140"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUMTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476288112","data":{"timestamp":" 947476288111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" WENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476288917","data":{"timestamp":" 947476288917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476290078","data":{"timestamp":" 947476290077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUMTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476294477","data":{"timestamp":" 947476294476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476295973","data":{"timestamp":" 947476295973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476297231","data":{"timestamp":" 947476297230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEKEZA"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476298469","data":{"timestamp":" 947476298469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEKEZA"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476300529","data":{"timestamp":" 947476300528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEKEZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476302320","data":{"timestamp":" 947476302320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476304003","data":{"timestamp":" 947476304002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EKENO"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476306011","data":{"timestamp":" 947476306011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINGIA"," userResponse":" ALIINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476307436","data":{"timestamp":" 947476307436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" ALIINGIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476308664","data":{"timestamp":" 947476308664"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476310546","data":{"timestamp":" 947476310546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476311213","data":{"timestamp":" 947476311212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476312661","data":{"timestamp":" 947476312660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEKEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWAELEKEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476313178","data":{"timestamp":" 947476313177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476314248","data":{"timestamp":" 947476314248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EKENO"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476315121","data":{"timestamp":" 947476315120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINGIA"," userResponse":" ALIINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476316090","data":{"timestamp":" 947476316089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476319886","data":{"timestamp":" 947476319885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMINI"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476320935","data":{"timestamp":" 947476320935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMINI"," userResponse":" START_WALIAMINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476323109","data":{"timestamp":" 947476323108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMINI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476324179","data":{"timestamp":" 947476324178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476325077","data":{"timestamp":" 947476325077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELIWA"," userResponse":" AMELIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476326166","data":{"timestamp":" 947476326166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476326607","data":{"timestamp":" 947476326607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476329052","data":{"timestamp":" 947476329052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMINI"," userResponse":" WALIAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476329679","data":{"timestamp":" 947476329679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476330386","data":{"timestamp":" 947476330385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELIWA"," userResponse":" AMELIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476330596","data":{"timestamp":" 947476330595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476331202","data":{"timestamp":" 947476331202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476333946","data":{"timestamp":" 947476333944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476334070","data":{"timestamp":" 947476334070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 15cc74ce-b58b-4738-acef-6c7eb8e3daa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476350352","data":{"timestamp":" 947476350351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476355142","data":{"timestamp":" 947476355141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476356739","data":{"timestamp":" 947476356738"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476359227","data":{"timestamp":" 947476359227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476360876","data":{"timestamp":" 947476360875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476363772","data":{"timestamp":" 947476363772"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476365367","data":{"timestamp":" 947476365367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476368077","data":{"timestamp":" 947476368076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476369714","data":{"timestamp":" 947476369714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476372458","data":{"timestamp":" 947476372458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476374061","data":{"timestamp":" 947476374061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" VITUMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476377344","data":{"timestamp":" 947476377344"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" VITUMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476378997","data":{"timestamp":" 947476378996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476385773","data":{"timestamp":" 947476385773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476387404","data":{"timestamp":" 947476387403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mboga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476390052","data":{"timestamp":" 947476390052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mboga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476391680","data":{"timestamp":" 947476391680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476394332","data":{"timestamp":" 947476394331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476395921","data":{"timestamp":" 947476395920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476398830","data":{"timestamp":" 947476398829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476400438","data":{"timestamp":" 947476400438"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476403456","data":{"timestamp":" 947476403456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476405107","data":{"timestamp":" 947476405106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyanya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476407870","data":{"timestamp":" 947476407869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyanya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476409489","data":{"timestamp":" 947476409489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476411981","data":{"timestamp":" 947476411981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476413601","data":{"timestamp":" 947476413600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mandazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANDAZI"," userResponse":" MANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476418661","data":{"timestamp":" 947476418660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mandazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANDAZI"," userResponse":" MANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476420297","data":{"timestamp":" 947476420296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476423057","data":{"timestamp":" 947476423056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476424696","data":{"timestamp":" 947476424694"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476427620","data":{"timestamp":" 947476427619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476429243","data":{"timestamp":" 947476429243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maharage"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476432189","data":{"timestamp":" 947476432188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maharage"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476433806","data":{"timestamp":" 947476433806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476436247","data":{"timestamp":" 947476436246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476438274","data":{"timestamp":" 947476438272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476438391","data":{"timestamp":" 947476438391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 41b94aa7-0b7e-405f-becd-bfa8e5561d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476452594","data":{"timestamp":" 947476452593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mboga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476455210","data":{"timestamp":" 947476455209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mboga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476456801","data":{"timestamp":" 947476456800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476459407","data":{"timestamp":" 947476459406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476461021","data":{"timestamp":" 947476461020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476463736","data":{"timestamp":" 947476463735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476465340","data":{"timestamp":" 947476465339"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyanya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476468025","data":{"timestamp":" 947476468024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyanya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476469644","data":{"timestamp":" 947476469644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476472121","data":{"timestamp":" 947476472121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" START_MAZIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476474047","data":{"timestamp":" 947476474047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476475637","data":{"timestamp":" 947476475636"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mandazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANDAZI"," userResponse":" MANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476478315","data":{"timestamp":" 947476478315"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mandazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MANDAZI"," userResponse":" START_MANDAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476480249","data":{"timestamp":" 947476480248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mandazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANDAZI"," userResponse":" MANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476481857","data":{"timestamp":" 947476481856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476484485","data":{"timestamp":" 947476484485"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476486093","data":{"timestamp":" 947476486092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476488702","data":{"timestamp":" 947476488701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476490310","data":{"timestamp":" 947476490310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476493186","data":{"timestamp":" 947476493186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476494783","data":{"timestamp":" 947476494783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476497273","data":{"timestamp":" 947476497272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476498864","data":{"timestamp":" 947476498863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476501581","data":{"timestamp":" 947476501580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476503191","data":{"timestamp":" 947476503191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476505912","data":{"timestamp":" 947476505911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476507510","data":{"timestamp":" 947476507510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" VITUMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476510575","data":{"timestamp":" 947476510574"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" VITUMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476512173","data":{"timestamp":" 947476512172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476515062","data":{"timestamp":" 947476515061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476516677","data":{"timestamp":" 947476516676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476522625","data":{"timestamp":" 947476522625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476524242","data":{"timestamp":" 947476524242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476526826","data":{"timestamp":" 947476526825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476528438","data":{"timestamp":" 947476528437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476531384","data":{"timestamp":" 947476531383"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476532993","data":{"timestamp":" 947476532993"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maharage"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476535936","data":{"timestamp":" 947476535935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maharage"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476537963","data":{"timestamp":" 947476537961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" maharage"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476538071","data":{"timestamp":" 947476538071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e6920f5b-a864-4204-aea0-34d8efdc087f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maharage"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476559691","data":{"timestamp":" 947476559691"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476560775","data":{"timestamp":" 947476560774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476566310","data":{"timestamp":" 947476566310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476567381","data":{"timestamp":" 947476567380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476571692","data":{"timestamp":" 947476571691"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476572754","data":{"timestamp":" 947476572754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476577260","data":{"timestamp":" 947476577259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476578323","data":{"timestamp":" 947476578322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476583000","data":{"timestamp":" 947476582999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476584084","data":{"timestamp":" 947476584083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476589116","data":{"timestamp":" 947476589116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476590177","data":{"timestamp":" 947476590176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476594901","data":{"timestamp":" 947476594901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyanya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476595956","data":{"timestamp":" 947476595955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyanya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476601437","data":{"timestamp":" 947476601436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" START_VITUMBUA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476607575","data":{"timestamp":" 947476607575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" VITUMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476608641","data":{"timestamp":" 947476608640"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" VITUMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476613496","data":{"timestamp":" 947476613495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" START_MAZIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476618219","data":{"timestamp":" 947476618218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476619287","data":{"timestamp":" 947476619287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476623882","data":{"timestamp":" 947476623881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476624941","data":{"timestamp":" 947476624940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476629294","data":{"timestamp":" 947476629294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maharage"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" START_MAHARAGE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476630923","data":{"timestamp":" 947476630922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maharage"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476631993","data":{"timestamp":" 947476631993"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maharage"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476638128","data":{"timestamp":" 947476638127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mandazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANDAZI"," userResponse":" MANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476639209","data":{"timestamp":" 947476639209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mandazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANDAZI"," userResponse":" MANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476643941","data":{"timestamp":" 947476643941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476645008","data":{"timestamp":" 947476645007"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476648671","data":{"timestamp":" 947476648670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mboga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476649741","data":{"timestamp":" 947476649740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mboga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476652824","data":{"timestamp":" 947476652823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476653889","data":{"timestamp":" 947476653889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476658610","data":{"timestamp":" 947476658609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476659670","data":{"timestamp":" 947476659669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476664876","data":{"timestamp":" 947476664875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476665944","data":{"timestamp":" 947476665943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476672921","data":{"timestamp":" 947476672920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476673994","data":{"timestamp":" 947476673993"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476677852","data":{"timestamp":" 947476677851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476677976","data":{"timestamp":" 947476677976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476696275","data":{"timestamp":" 947476696275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476707875","data":{"timestamp":" 947476707875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" e8a4057c-b430-49d0-a156-748207478af7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476727315","data":{"timestamp":" 947476727315"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b36c699d-fb0f-47a7-9411-8354532b945a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyanya_nyanya-maji-mandazi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyanya"," userResponse":" nyanya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476732012","data":{"timestamp":" 947476732011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b36c699d-fb0f-47a7-9411-8354532b945a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyama_nyama-nyanya-embe"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyama"," userResponse":" nyama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476737757","data":{"timestamp":" 947476737757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b36c699d-fb0f-47a7-9411-8354532b945a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_chai_viazi-vitumbua-chai"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chai"," userResponse":" chai"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476742987","data":{"timestamp":" 947476742987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b36c699d-fb0f-47a7-9411-8354532b945a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vitumbua_vitumbua-chai-nyanya"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vitumbua"," userResponse":" vitumbua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476747927","data":{"timestamp":" 947476747926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b36c699d-fb0f-47a7-9411-8354532b945a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndizi_ndizi-karoti-vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndizi"," userResponse":" ndizi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476752936","data":{"timestamp":" 947476752935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b36c699d-fb0f-47a7-9411-8354532b945a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_maji_maji-embe-maziwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" maji"," userResponse":" maji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476758233","data":{"timestamp":" 947476758233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b36c699d-fb0f-47a7-9411-8354532b945a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ugali_ugali-ndizi-maharage"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ugali"," userResponse":" ugali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476763208","data":{"timestamp":" 947476763208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b36c699d-fb0f-47a7-9411-8354532b945a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wali_nyanya-wali-mandazi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wali"," userResponse":" wali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476773252","data":{"timestamp":" 947476773252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b36c699d-fb0f-47a7-9411-8354532b945a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_chakula_mandazi-chakula-chai"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chakula"," userResponse":" chakula"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476779060","data":{"timestamp":" 947476779060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b36c699d-fb0f-47a7-9411-8354532b945a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_karoti_karoti-wali-nyama"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" karoti"," userResponse":" karoti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476784840","data":{"timestamp":" 947476784838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b36c699d-fb0f-47a7-9411-8354532b945a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_karoti_karoti-wali-nyama"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476811087","data":{"timestamp":" 947476811086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 321ee5e5-c703-4972-b8fe-516b6071bd9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_chapati_ugali_mboga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476817735","data":{"timestamp":" 947476817735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 321ee5e5-c703-4972-b8fe-516b6071bd9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nyanya_maziwa_karoti"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476824415","data":{"timestamp":" 947476824414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 321ee5e5-c703-4972-b8fe-516b6071bd9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_samaki_maziwa_chai"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476831060","data":{"timestamp":" 947476831059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 321ee5e5-c703-4972-b8fe-516b6071bd9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vitumbua_wali_karoti"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476837717","data":{"timestamp":" 947476837717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 321ee5e5-c703-4972-b8fe-516b6071bd9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_samaki_mboga_chakula"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476845168","data":{"timestamp":" 947476845168"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 321ee5e5-c703-4972-b8fe-516b6071bd9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_samaki_mboga_chakula"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476851841","data":{"timestamp":" 947476851841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 321ee5e5-c703-4972-b8fe-516b6071bd9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ugali_mandazi_maharage"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476858501","data":{"timestamp":" 947476858501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 321ee5e5-c703-4972-b8fe-516b6071bd9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nyama_chakula_chapati"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476865154","data":{"timestamp":" 947476865153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 321ee5e5-c703-4972-b8fe-516b6071bd9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_karoti_mboga_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476871815","data":{"timestamp":" 947476871815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 321ee5e5-c703-4972-b8fe-516b6071bd9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_maziwa_nyama_nyanya"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476878477","data":{"timestamp":" 947476878477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 321ee5e5-c703-4972-b8fe-516b6071bd9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_maji_karoti_embe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476890550","data":{"timestamp":" 947476890550"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 321ee5e5-c703-4972-b8fe-516b6071bd9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_maji_karoti_embe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476904508","data":{"timestamp":" 947476904507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476905375","data":{"timestamp":" 947476905374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476906412","data":{"timestamp":" 947476906412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476906669","data":{"timestamp":" 947476906668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476907248","data":{"timestamp":" 947476907248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476907826","data":{"timestamp":" 947476907825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476908374","data":{"timestamp":" 947476908373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476910647","data":{"timestamp":" 947476910646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" START_WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476911815","data":{"timestamp":" 947476911815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476913462","data":{"timestamp":" 947476913461"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476914838","data":{"timestamp":" 947476914838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476915969","data":{"timestamp":" 947476915968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_MWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476917192","data":{"timestamp":" 947476917191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476918862","data":{"timestamp":" 947476918861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476920638","data":{"timestamp":" 947476920638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476920645","data":{"timestamp":" 947476920645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476921134","data":{"timestamp":" 947476921134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476922454","data":{"timestamp":" 947476922453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476925511","data":{"timestamp":" 947476925510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAFUTA"," userResponse":" ALITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476926267","data":{"timestamp":" 947476926267"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476926673","data":{"timestamp":" 947476926672"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476927502","data":{"timestamp":" 947476927501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476928585","data":{"timestamp":" 947476928585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476929391","data":{"timestamp":" 947476929390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476931871","data":{"timestamp":" 947476931871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAFUTA"," userResponse":" START_ALITAFUTA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476933533","data":{"timestamp":" 947476933532"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAFUTA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476935422","data":{"timestamp":" 947476935421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAFUTA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476936701","data":{"timestamp":" 947476936700"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476938297","data":{"timestamp":" 947476938297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476938784","data":{"timestamp":" 947476938783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476942351","data":{"timestamp":" 947476942351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" START_ALITAFUTA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476943934","data":{"timestamp":" 947476943933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476944500","data":{"timestamp":" 947476944500"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" START_ALITAFUTA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476946335","data":{"timestamp":" 947476946335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476948162","data":{"timestamp":" 947476948162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476950720","data":{"timestamp":" 947476950720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476952276","data":{"timestamp":" 947476952275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASHAMBULIA"," userResponse":" ANASHAMBULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476955277","data":{"timestamp":" 947476955276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476955409","data":{"timestamp":" 947476955409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANASHAMBULIA"," userResponse":" START_ANASHAMBULIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476956606","data":{"timestamp":" 947476956605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANASHAMBULIA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476958693","data":{"timestamp":" 947476958693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASHAMBULIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476960999","data":{"timestamp":" 947476960997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476961272","data":{"timestamp":" 947476961271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476962003","data":{"timestamp":" 947476962002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476962821","data":{"timestamp":" 947476962821"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476963288","data":{"timestamp":" 947476963288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476964000","data":{"timestamp":" 947476963999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476964738","data":{"timestamp":" 947476964738"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476965949","data":{"timestamp":" 947476965948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFURAHI"," userResponse":" ANAFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476968187","data":{"timestamp":" 947476968186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476968496","data":{"timestamp":" 947476968496"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476969088","data":{"timestamp":" 947476969087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476970372","data":{"timestamp":" 947476970372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476970789","data":{"timestamp":" 947476970789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476971302","data":{"timestamp":" 947476971302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476972187","data":{"timestamp":" 947476972187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476972928","data":{"timestamp":" 947476972928"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFURAHI"," userResponse":" START_ANAFURAHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476974847","data":{"timestamp":" 947476974846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFURAHI"," userResponse":" ANAFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476977692","data":{"timestamp":" 947476977691"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476978766","data":{"timestamp":" 947476978765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOHISI"," userResponse":" ANAPOHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476979312","data":{"timestamp":" 947476979312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476979928","data":{"timestamp":" 947476979928"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476981767","data":{"timestamp":" 947476981766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476982847","data":{"timestamp":" 947476982847"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOHISI"," userResponse":" ANAPOHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476983566","data":{"timestamp":" 947476983565"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476984253","data":{"timestamp":" 947476984253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476986277","data":{"timestamp":" 947476986276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947476986363","data":{"timestamp":" 947476986362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 177b1a90-8750-4ad9-a133-351067cae8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477003466","data":{"timestamp":" 947477003465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477005118","data":{"timestamp":" 947477005117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477010602","data":{"timestamp":" 947477010601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477016961","data":{"timestamp":" 947477016961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477018354","data":{"timestamp":" 947477018353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_PALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477020003","data":{"timestamp":" 947477020002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_PALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477021678","data":{"timestamp":" 947477021678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477022951","data":{"timestamp":" 947477022951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477022971","data":{"timestamp":" 947477022971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477024256","data":{"timestamp":" 947477024255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" START_MWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477025196","data":{"timestamp":" 947477025196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477026720","data":{"timestamp":" 947477026719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477027886","data":{"timestamp":" 947477027886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477029786","data":{"timestamp":" 947477029785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477030648","data":{"timestamp":" 947477030648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477031684","data":{"timestamp":" 947477031684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477031941","data":{"timestamp":" 947477031941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477032503","data":{"timestamp":" 947477032503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477033068","data":{"timestamp":" 947477033067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477033601","data":{"timestamp":" 947477033601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477038388","data":{"timestamp":" 947477038387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAFUTA"," userResponse":" ALITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477039800","data":{"timestamp":" 947477039800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477040897","data":{"timestamp":" 947477040897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477041813","data":{"timestamp":" 947477041813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477041825","data":{"timestamp":" 947477041824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477043729","data":{"timestamp":" 947477043729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477046355","data":{"timestamp":" 947477046355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477048894","data":{"timestamp":" 947477048893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAFUTA"," userResponse":" ALITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477049650","data":{"timestamp":" 947477049649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477050055","data":{"timestamp":" 947477050054"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477050890","data":{"timestamp":" 947477050890"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477051973","data":{"timestamp":" 947477051973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477052784","data":{"timestamp":" 947477052784"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477057106","data":{"timestamp":" 947477057105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477058037","data":{"timestamp":" 947477058037"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANASHAMBULIA"," userResponse":" START_ANASHAMBULIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477059269","data":{"timestamp":" 947477059269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANASHAMBULIA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477061422","data":{"timestamp":" 947477061422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASHAMBULIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477063411","data":{"timestamp":" 947477063410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477064968","data":{"timestamp":" 947477064967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASHAMBULIA"," userResponse":" ANASHAMBULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477068030","data":{"timestamp":" 947477068030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477071435","data":{"timestamp":" 947477071434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477073053","data":{"timestamp":" 947477073052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477073817","data":{"timestamp":" 947477073817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477074512","data":{"timestamp":" 947477074512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477075437","data":{"timestamp":" 947477075436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477076808","data":{"timestamp":" 947477076807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477077311","data":{"timestamp":" 947477077311"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477077809","data":{"timestamp":" 947477077809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477078923","data":{"timestamp":" 947477078923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477080099","data":{"timestamp":" 947477080099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFURAHI"," userResponse":" ANAFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477081854","data":{"timestamp":" 947477081853"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477082127","data":{"timestamp":" 947477082127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477082864","data":{"timestamp":" 947477082864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477083679","data":{"timestamp":" 947477083679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477084155","data":{"timestamp":" 947477084154"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477084872","data":{"timestamp":" 947477084872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477085610","data":{"timestamp":" 947477085609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477086821","data":{"timestamp":" 947477086820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFURAHI"," userResponse":" ANAFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477090354","data":{"timestamp":" 947477090353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477093978","data":{"timestamp":" 947477093978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOHISI"," userResponse":" ANAPOHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477095137","data":{"timestamp":" 947477095137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477096268","data":{"timestamp":" 947477096267"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477098594","data":{"timestamp":" 947477098593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477099672","data":{"timestamp":" 947477099672"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOHISI"," userResponse":" ANAPOHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477100218","data":{"timestamp":" 947477100217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477100833","data":{"timestamp":" 947477100832"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477103719","data":{"timestamp":" 947477103717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477103835","data":{"timestamp":" 947477103834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 8c04e549-4fb1-4409-ac3f-180690dcfee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477121492","data":{"timestamp":" 947477121492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" songura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SONGURA"," userResponse":" SONGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477126752","data":{"timestamp":" 947477126751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" songura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SONGURA"," userResponse":" SONGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477128377","data":{"timestamp":" 947477128376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477133106","data":{"timestamp":" 947477133105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477134745","data":{"timestamp":" 947477134744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477137337","data":{"timestamp":" 947477137336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477138982","data":{"timestamp":" 947477138981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" MBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477143710","data":{"timestamp":" 947477143709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" MBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477145294","data":{"timestamp":" 947477145293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" farasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" FARASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477148186","data":{"timestamp":" 947477148185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" farasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" FARASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477149802","data":{"timestamp":" 947477149801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477152552","data":{"timestamp":" 947477152552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477154155","data":{"timestamp":" 947477154154"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477162284","data":{"timestamp":" 947477162283"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477163916","data":{"timestamp":" 947477163915"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477166768","data":{"timestamp":" 947477166767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477168369","data":{"timestamp":" 947477168369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477170721","data":{"timestamp":" 947477170721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477172340","data":{"timestamp":" 947477172340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477174969","data":{"timestamp":" 947477174968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477176571","data":{"timestamp":" 947477176570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" CHUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477178938","data":{"timestamp":" 947477178938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" CHUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477180561","data":{"timestamp":" 947477180560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477183058","data":{"timestamp":" 947477183057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477184674","data":{"timestamp":" 947477184673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyoka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477186999","data":{"timestamp":" 947477186999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyoka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477188636","data":{"timestamp":" 947477188635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477192643","data":{"timestamp":" 947477192643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477194286","data":{"timestamp":" 947477194286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477196988","data":{"timestamp":" 947477196988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477198606","data":{"timestamp":" 947477198606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477198625","data":{"timestamp":" 947477198625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477201011","data":{"timestamp":" 947477201010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477201612","data":{"timestamp":" 947477201611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477203223","data":{"timestamp":" 947477203222"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477205830","data":{"timestamp":" 947477205829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477207471","data":{"timestamp":" 947477207470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477210072","data":{"timestamp":" 947477210072"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477211733","data":{"timestamp":" 947477211732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477216709","data":{"timestamp":" 947477216709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477218738","data":{"timestamp":" 947477218737"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477218864","data":{"timestamp":" 947477218864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" c126f2d7-4820-42c8-b525-e48fe2b40ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477231736","data":{"timestamp":" 947477231736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477234198","data":{"timestamp":" 947477234198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477235798","data":{"timestamp":" 947477235797"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" farasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" FARASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477240960","data":{"timestamp":" 947477240960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" farasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" START_FARASI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477243780","data":{"timestamp":" 947477243780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" farasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" START_FARASI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477245299","data":{"timestamp":" 947477245298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" farasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477246929","data":{"timestamp":" 947477246928"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477249473","data":{"timestamp":" 947477249472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477251094","data":{"timestamp":" 947477251094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477259685","data":{"timestamp":" 947477259685"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477261294","data":{"timestamp":" 947477261293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477267331","data":{"timestamp":" 947477267330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477268939","data":{"timestamp":" 947477268938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477271642","data":{"timestamp":" 947477271641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477273238","data":{"timestamp":" 947477273238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyoka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477275942","data":{"timestamp":" 947477275941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyoka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477277568","data":{"timestamp":" 947477277567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477279846","data":{"timestamp":" 947477279846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477281425","data":{"timestamp":" 947477281425"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477283784","data":{"timestamp":" 947477283783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477285417","data":{"timestamp":" 947477285416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477285442","data":{"timestamp":" 947477285442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477287904","data":{"timestamp":" 947477287903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477289921","data":{"timestamp":" 947477289920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477291052","data":{"timestamp":" 947477291052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477292618","data":{"timestamp":" 947477292617"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477295196","data":{"timestamp":" 947477295195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477296795","data":{"timestamp":" 947477296794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477299206","data":{"timestamp":" 947477299205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477300799","data":{"timestamp":" 947477300798"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" MBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477303729","data":{"timestamp":" 947477303729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" START_MBUNI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477307445","data":{"timestamp":" 947477307445"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" MBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477309077","data":{"timestamp":" 947477309077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477311732","data":{"timestamp":" 947477311731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477313360","data":{"timestamp":" 947477313359"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477315765","data":{"timestamp":" 947477315765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477317384","data":{"timestamp":" 947477317383"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477319932","data":{"timestamp":" 947477319932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477321542","data":{"timestamp":" 947477321541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" songura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SONGURA"," userResponse":" SONGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477324289","data":{"timestamp":" 947477324289"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" songura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SONGURA"," userResponse":" SONGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477325868","data":{"timestamp":" 947477325868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477328504","data":{"timestamp":" 947477328504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" START_MBUZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477330232","data":{"timestamp":" 947477330231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477331849","data":{"timestamp":" 947477331848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" CHUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477334411","data":{"timestamp":" 947477334411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" CHUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477336441","data":{"timestamp":" 947477336439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477336531","data":{"timestamp":" 947477336531"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" af012515-1bd0-421d-9ad1-bdbeac41d461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" CHUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477351039","data":{"timestamp":" 947477351038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" CHUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477352087","data":{"timestamp":" 947477352086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" CHUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477356366","data":{"timestamp":" 947477356365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477356473","data":{"timestamp":" 947477356473"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477357548","data":{"timestamp":" 947477357547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477357568","data":{"timestamp":" 947477357568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477369489","data":{"timestamp":" 947477369489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477370552","data":{"timestamp":" 947477370551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477372115","data":{"timestamp":" 947477372114"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyoka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477373205","data":{"timestamp":" 947477373204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyoka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477378544","data":{"timestamp":" 947477378543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477379623","data":{"timestamp":" 947477379622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477384439","data":{"timestamp":" 947477384439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477385490","data":{"timestamp":" 947477385489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477389711","data":{"timestamp":" 947477389711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477390768","data":{"timestamp":" 947477390768"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477395364","data":{"timestamp":" 947477395363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" farasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" START_FARASI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477397294","data":{"timestamp":" 947477397293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" farasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" FARASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477398364","data":{"timestamp":" 947477398364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" farasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" FARASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477402880","data":{"timestamp":" 947477402879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" songura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SONGURA"," userResponse":" SONGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477403940","data":{"timestamp":" 947477403939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" songura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SONGURA"," userResponse":" SONGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477408491","data":{"timestamp":" 947477408491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477409559","data":{"timestamp":" 947477409558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477413550","data":{"timestamp":" 947477413549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" MBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477414607","data":{"timestamp":" 947477414606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" MBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477418531","data":{"timestamp":" 947477418530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477419592","data":{"timestamp":" 947477419591"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477424358","data":{"timestamp":" 947477424357"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477425425","data":{"timestamp":" 947477425424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477429599","data":{"timestamp":" 947477429598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477430663","data":{"timestamp":" 947477430663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477435807","data":{"timestamp":" 947477435807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477436867","data":{"timestamp":" 947477436867"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477440307","data":{"timestamp":" 947477440306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477441359","data":{"timestamp":" 947477441358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477446556","data":{"timestamp":" 947477446555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477447620","data":{"timestamp":" 947477447620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477452433","data":{"timestamp":" 947477452433"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477453504","data":{"timestamp":" 947477453503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477457771","data":{"timestamp":" 947477457771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477458829","data":{"timestamp":" 947477458828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477462274","data":{"timestamp":" 947477462272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477462367","data":{"timestamp":" 947477462367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 7e223540-18f2-4d76-9b79-a3efa99772a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477479029","data":{"timestamp":" 947477479029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef8b2101-335b-4a6f-905b-c1822a08e916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_chura_bata-chura-punda"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chura"," userResponse":" chura"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477484643","data":{"timestamp":" 947477484643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef8b2101-335b-4a6f-905b-c1822a08e916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kondoo_kondoo-panya-farasi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kondoo"," userResponse":" kondoo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477491171","data":{"timestamp":" 947477491171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef8b2101-335b-4a6f-905b-c1822a08e916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fisi_songura-fisi-punda"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fisi"," userResponse":" fisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477497282","data":{"timestamp":" 947477497282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef8b2101-335b-4a6f-905b-c1822a08e916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuni_songura-mbuni-paka"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbuni"," userResponse":" mbuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477502362","data":{"timestamp":" 947477502362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef8b2101-335b-4a6f-905b-c1822a08e916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_twiga_punda-twiga-panya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" twiga"," userResponse":" twiga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477509018","data":{"timestamp":" 947477509018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef8b2101-335b-4a6f-905b-c1822a08e916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbwa_chura-mbwa-tembo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbwa"," userResponse":" mbwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477514039","data":{"timestamp":" 947477514039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef8b2101-335b-4a6f-905b-c1822a08e916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_paka_paka-kondoo-ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" paka"," userResponse":" paka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477519391","data":{"timestamp":" 947477519391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef8b2101-335b-4a6f-905b-c1822a08e916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_panya_panya-paka-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" panya"," userResponse":" panya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477524507","data":{"timestamp":" 947477524507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef8b2101-335b-4a6f-905b-c1822a08e916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bata_mbuni-bata-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bata"," userResponse":" bata"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477530258","data":{"timestamp":" 947477530258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef8b2101-335b-4a6f-905b-c1822a08e916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuku_ng'ombe-kuku-tembo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuku"," userResponse":" kuku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477536044","data":{"timestamp":" 947477536041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" ef8b2101-335b-4a6f-905b-c1822a08e916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kuku_ng'ombe-kuku-tembo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477556367","data":{"timestamp":" 947477556367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 97d2c8aa-47fc-4fa2-97c9-31ce5a695a03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyoka_chura-nyoka-kuku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyoka"," userResponse":" nyoka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477561839","data":{"timestamp":" 947477561839"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 97d2c8aa-47fc-4fa2-97c9-31ce5a695a03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_chui_twiga-fisi-chui"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chui"," userResponse":" chui"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477569526","data":{"timestamp":" 947477569526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 97d2c8aa-47fc-4fa2-97c9-31ce5a695a03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuzi_chura-mbwa-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbuzi"," userResponse":" mbuzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477574964","data":{"timestamp":" 947477574964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 97d2c8aa-47fc-4fa2-97c9-31ce5a695a03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fisi_kondoo-fisi-panya"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fisi"," userResponse":" fisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477584226","data":{"timestamp":" 947477584226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 97d2c8aa-47fc-4fa2-97c9-31ce5a695a03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bata_bata-farasi-kuku"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bata"," userResponse":" kuku"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477591054","data":{"timestamp":" 947477591054"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 97d2c8aa-47fc-4fa2-97c9-31ce5a695a03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bata_bata-farasi-kuku"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bata"," userResponse":" bata"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477595827","data":{"timestamp":" 947477595826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 97d2c8aa-47fc-4fa2-97c9-31ce5a695a03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbwa_mbwa-chui-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbwa"," userResponse":" mbwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477600718","data":{"timestamp":" 947477600718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 97d2c8aa-47fc-4fa2-97c9-31ce5a695a03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_panya_bata-panya-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" panya"," userResponse":" bata"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477606519","data":{"timestamp":" 947477606519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 97d2c8aa-47fc-4fa2-97c9-31ce5a695a03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_panya_bata-panya-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" panya"," userResponse":" panya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477612069","data":{"timestamp":" 947477612069"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 97d2c8aa-47fc-4fa2-97c9-31ce5a695a03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_punda_simba-punda-songura"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" punda"," userResponse":" punda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477617240","data":{"timestamp":" 947477617240"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 97d2c8aa-47fc-4fa2-97c9-31ce5a695a03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuku_ng'ombe-kuku-mbuni"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuku"," userResponse":" kuku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477622177","data":{"timestamp":" 947477622176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 97d2c8aa-47fc-4fa2-97c9-31ce5a695a03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_chura_chura-farasi-panya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chura"," userResponse":" chura"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477627970","data":{"timestamp":" 947477627969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 97d2c8aa-47fc-4fa2-97c9-31ce5a695a03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_chura_chura-farasi-panya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477652375","data":{"timestamp":" 947477652375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b39e09ee-03ba-4a2f-875a-d5fc39120137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nyoka_simba_farasi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477659004","data":{"timestamp":" 947477659004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b39e09ee-03ba-4a2f-875a-d5fc39120137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mbwa_punda_nyoka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477666575","data":{"timestamp":" 947477666575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b39e09ee-03ba-4a2f-875a-d5fc39120137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mbwa_punda_nyoka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477673244","data":{"timestamp":" 947477673243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b39e09ee-03ba-4a2f-875a-d5fc39120137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_punda_twiga_paka"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477679861","data":{"timestamp":" 947477679861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b39e09ee-03ba-4a2f-875a-d5fc39120137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fisi_chura_chui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477686499","data":{"timestamp":" 947477686498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b39e09ee-03ba-4a2f-875a-d5fc39120137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fisi_mbuzi_songura"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477693970","data":{"timestamp":" 947477693970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b39e09ee-03ba-4a2f-875a-d5fc39120137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fisi_mbuzi_songura"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477700654","data":{"timestamp":" 947477700654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b39e09ee-03ba-4a2f-875a-d5fc39120137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kondoo_twiga_mbwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477707339","data":{"timestamp":" 947477707338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b39e09ee-03ba-4a2f-875a-d5fc39120137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mbuni_songura_mbwa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477713965","data":{"timestamp":" 947477713964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b39e09ee-03ba-4a2f-875a-d5fc39120137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nyoka_simba_mbuni"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477720610","data":{"timestamp":" 947477720609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b39e09ee-03ba-4a2f-875a-d5fc39120137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ng'ombe_mbuni_nyoka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477727304","data":{"timestamp":" 947477727303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b39e09ee-03ba-4a2f-875a-d5fc39120137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fisi_punda_panya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477735147","data":{"timestamp":" 947477735146"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" b39e09ee-03ba-4a2f-875a-d5fc39120137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_fisi_punda_panya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477765850","data":{"timestamp":" 947477765849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_twiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477769032","data":{"timestamp":" 947477769032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_twiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477771480","data":{"timestamp":" 947477771480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_twiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477778146","data":{"timestamp":" 947477778146"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_twiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477782088","data":{"timestamp":" 947477782088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_twiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477785337","data":{"timestamp":" 947477785337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_twiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477802404","data":{"timestamp":" 947477802404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chui"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477806129","data":{"timestamp":" 947477806129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chui"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477809256","data":{"timestamp":" 947477809256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chui"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477811826","data":{"timestamp":" 947477811825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chui"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477820231","data":{"timestamp":" 947477820231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_simba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477822848","data":{"timestamp":" 947477822848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_simba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477828820","data":{"timestamp":" 947477828820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_simba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477832858","data":{"timestamp":" 947477832857"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_simba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477841209","data":{"timestamp":" 947477841209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_simba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477844705","data":{"timestamp":" 947477844705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_simba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477848057","data":{"timestamp":" 947477848057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_simba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477865077","data":{"timestamp":" 947477865077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fisi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477867903","data":{"timestamp":" 947477867903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fisi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477874465","data":{"timestamp":" 947477874464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fisi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477877019","data":{"timestamp":" 947477877019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fisi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477879261","data":{"timestamp":" 947477879261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fisi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477894764","data":{"timestamp":" 947477894764"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_farasi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477897755","data":{"timestamp":" 947477897755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_farasi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477900729","data":{"timestamp":" 947477900728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_farasi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477904092","data":{"timestamp":" 947477904092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_farasi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477907803","data":{"timestamp":" 947477907803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_farasi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477910766","data":{"timestamp":" 947477910766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_farasi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477917215","data":{"timestamp":" 947477917215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_farasi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477935181","data":{"timestamp":" 947477935181"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kondoo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477938569","data":{"timestamp":" 947477938569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kondoo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477942685","data":{"timestamp":" 947477942684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kondoo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477946796","data":{"timestamp":" 947477946795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kondoo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477950131","data":{"timestamp":" 947477950131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kondoo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477953157","data":{"timestamp":" 947477953156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kondoo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477962763","data":{"timestamp":" 947477962763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_paka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477970535","data":{"timestamp":" 947477970535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_paka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477973513","data":{"timestamp":" 947477973513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_paka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477977184","data":{"timestamp":" 947477977184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_paka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477979827","data":{"timestamp":" 947477979827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_paka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477994501","data":{"timestamp":" 947477994500"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947477997980","data":{"timestamp":" 947477997980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478000761","data":{"timestamp":" 947478000760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478004212","data":{"timestamp":" 947478004212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478006679","data":{"timestamp":" 947478006679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478015436","data":{"timestamp":" 947478015436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478017727","data":{"timestamp":" 947478017727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478020983","data":{"timestamp":" 947478020983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478027636","data":{"timestamp":" 947478027635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478035242","data":{"timestamp":" 947478035242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478038097","data":{"timestamp":" 947478038097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478052196","data":{"timestamp":" 947478052196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbuni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478055018","data":{"timestamp":" 947478055017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbuni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478057363","data":{"timestamp":" 947478057363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbuni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478060544","data":{"timestamp":" 947478060544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbuni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478063309","data":{"timestamp":" 947478063308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbuni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-animals.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478077025","data":{"timestamp":" 947478077022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 122bed4e-0685-4243-9a1c-ae01cc916efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-animals.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_mbuni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478091156","data":{"timestamp":" 947478091155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478099052","data":{"timestamp":" 947478099051"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478101616","data":{"timestamp":" 947478101615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478102058","data":{"timestamp":" 947478102057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDALO"," userResponse":" NDALO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478103721","data":{"timestamp":" 947478103720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478104255","data":{"timestamp":" 947478104254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478104521","data":{"timestamp":" 947478104520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478105150","data":{"timestamp":" 947478105149"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDALO"," userResponse":" NDALO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478107876","data":{"timestamp":" 947478107876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478109178","data":{"timestamp":" 947478109177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478110582","data":{"timestamp":" 947478110582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478110779","data":{"timestamp":" 947478110778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEMFUGA"," userResponse":" AMEMFUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478111374","data":{"timestamp":" 947478111374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478112991","data":{"timestamp":" 947478112991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478114481","data":{"timestamp":" 947478114481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478115894","data":{"timestamp":" 947478115894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAYEITWA"," userResponse":" AMEMFUGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478117547","data":{"timestamp":" 947478117547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAYEITWA"," userResponse":" START_ANAYEITWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478119464","data":{"timestamp":" 947478119464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAYEITWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478120140","data":{"timestamp":" 947478120140"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478120972","data":{"timestamp":" 947478120971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478122604","data":{"timestamp":" 947478122603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478123390","data":{"timestamp":" 947478123390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478124448","data":{"timestamp":" 947478124447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEMFUGA"," userResponse":" AMEMFUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478125052","data":{"timestamp":" 947478125052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478125075","data":{"timestamp":" 947478125074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478125756","data":{"timestamp":" 947478125756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478126829","data":{"timestamp":" 947478126828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAYEITWA"," userResponse":" ANAYEITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478127508","data":{"timestamp":" 947478127507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478130755","data":{"timestamp":" 947478130755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478132539","data":{"timestamp":" 947478132539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" START_ANAPENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478133890","data":{"timestamp":" 947478133889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478135595","data":{"timestamp":" 947478135594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478136995","data":{"timestamp":" 947478136995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478138423","data":{"timestamp":" 947478138423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" NZIMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478139738","data":{"timestamp":" 947478139738"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478140062","data":{"timestamp":" 947478140061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZIMA"," userResponse":" NZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478141810","data":{"timestamp":" 947478141810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478142799","data":{"timestamp":" 947478142798"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478143266","data":{"timestamp":" 947478143265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478143873","data":{"timestamp":" 947478143873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478144425","data":{"timestamp":" 947478144424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478145046","data":{"timestamp":" 947478145044"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZIMA"," userResponse":" NZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478149336","data":{"timestamp":" 947478149335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478150138","data":{"timestamp":" 947478150138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478151549","data":{"timestamp":" 947478151548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAMPA"," userResponse":" TUNAMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478152265","data":{"timestamp":" 947478152264"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFAKA"," userResponse":" NAFAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478154136","data":{"timestamp":" 947478154135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478155060","data":{"timestamp":" 947478155060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478156248","data":{"timestamp":" 947478156248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAMPA"," userResponse":" TUNAMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478157067","data":{"timestamp":" 947478157066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFAKA"," userResponse":" NAFAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478159816","data":{"timestamp":" 947478159815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478160938","data":{"timestamp":" 947478160937"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478162088","data":{"timestamp":" 947478162088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478163693","data":{"timestamp":" 947478163693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478164471","data":{"timestamp":" 947478164470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478165605","data":{"timestamp":" 947478165605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478167253","data":{"timestamp":" 947478167252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478167803","data":{"timestamp":" 947478167802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478168366","data":{"timestamp":" 947478168365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478168829","data":{"timestamp":" 947478168829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478169712","data":{"timestamp":" 947478169712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478171768","data":{"timestamp":" 947478171767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninampenda Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478178495","data":{"timestamp":" 947478178494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninampenda Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" START_NINAMPENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478179800","data":{"timestamp":" 947478179799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninampenda Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAMPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478180921","data":{"timestamp":" 947478180920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninampenda Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" START_NINAMPENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478181761","data":{"timestamp":" 947478181761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninampenda Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478183527","data":{"timestamp":" 947478183526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninampenda Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478184730","data":{"timestamp":" 947478184729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninampenda Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAMPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478185370","data":{"timestamp":" 947478185369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninampenda Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478189735","data":{"timestamp":" 947478189734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAMTUNZA"," userResponse":" START_TUNAMTUNZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478192296","data":{"timestamp":" 947478192296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAMTUNZA"," userResponse":" START_TUNAMTUNZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478194212","data":{"timestamp":" 947478194212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAMTUNZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478195478","data":{"timestamp":" 947478195478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478196913","data":{"timestamp":" 947478196912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478198792","data":{"timestamp":" 947478198792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANATUSAIDIA"," userResponse":" START_ANATUSAIDIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478199821","data":{"timestamp":" 947478199820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANATUSAIDIA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478201849","data":{"timestamp":" 947478201849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATUSAIDIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478202405","data":{"timestamp":" 947478202404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAMTUNZA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478204570","data":{"timestamp":" 947478204569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAMTUNZA"," userResponse":" TUNAMTUNZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478205123","data":{"timestamp":" 947478205122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478205399","data":{"timestamp":" 947478205398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478205566","data":{"timestamp":" 947478205565"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATUSAIDIA"," userResponse":" ANATUSAIDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478210663","data":{"timestamp":" 947478210662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatupa maziwa mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATUPA"," userResponse":" ANATUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478210812","data":{"timestamp":" 947478210812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatupa maziwa mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478212794","data":{"timestamp":" 947478212794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatupa maziwa mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478214642","data":{"timestamp":" 947478214642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatupa maziwa mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478216819","data":{"timestamp":" 947478216818"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatupa maziwa mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATUPA"," userResponse":" ANATUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478217803","data":{"timestamp":" 947478217802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatupa maziwa mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478219023","data":{"timestamp":" 947478219022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatupa maziwa mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478221808","data":{"timestamp":" 947478221808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" START_KUNINUNULIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478223002","data":{"timestamp":" 947478223001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" HUUZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478224495","data":{"timestamp":" 947478224495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478225468","data":{"timestamp":" 947478225467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" HUUZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478226653","data":{"timestamp":" 947478226653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478228138","data":{"timestamp":" 947478228137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478230620","data":{"timestamp":" 947478230620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUUZA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478232048","data":{"timestamp":" 947478232047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HUUZA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478233683","data":{"timestamp":" 947478233683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUUZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478235162","data":{"timestamp":" 947478235161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478240171","data":{"timestamp":" 947478240171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478240895","data":{"timestamp":" 947478240895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478243589","data":{"timestamp":" 947478243589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478245467","data":{"timestamp":" 947478245467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478247812","data":{"timestamp":" 947478247812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNINUNULIA"," userResponse":" START_BAADHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478249957","data":{"timestamp":" 947478249957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNINUNULIA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478252012","data":{"timestamp":" 947478252011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNINUNULIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478253614","data":{"timestamp":" 947478253614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VITABU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478255942","data":{"timestamp":" 947478255941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" VITABU"," userResponse":" HUUZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478257452","data":{"timestamp":" 947478257451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITABU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478259635","data":{"timestamp":" 947478259635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478259761","data":{"timestamp":" 947478259761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478261401","data":{"timestamp":" 947478261400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478261964","data":{"timestamp":" 947478261962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478262820","data":{"timestamp":" 947478262819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUUZA"," userResponse":" HUUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478263630","data":{"timestamp":" 947478263629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478263738","data":{"timestamp":" 947478263737"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478264599","data":{"timestamp":" 947478264598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478265382","data":{"timestamp":" 947478265381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478266684","data":{"timestamp":" 947478266683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNINUNULIA"," userResponse":" KUNINUNULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478267425","data":{"timestamp":" 947478267424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITABU"," userResponse":" VITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478267747","data":{"timestamp":" 947478267746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478268648","data":{"timestamp":" 947478268647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478272849","data":{"timestamp":" 947478272849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" START_KUSOMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478274089","data":{"timestamp":" 947478274088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478275774","data":{"timestamp":" 947478275773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478276942","data":{"timestamp":" 947478276941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478280365","data":{"timestamp":" 947478280364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" START_NINAPENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478282198","data":{"timestamp":" 947478282197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478283778","data":{"timestamp":" 947478283778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478286084","data":{"timestamp":" 947478286083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478287792","data":{"timestamp":" 947478287792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478288690","data":{"timestamp":" 947478288689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478289474","data":{"timestamp":" 947478289473"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478290319","data":{"timestamp":" 947478290319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478293209","data":{"timestamp":" 947478293208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478294094","data":{"timestamp":" 947478294093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEFAHAMU"," userResponse":" UMEFAHAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478295490","data":{"timestamp":" 947478295489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478297520","data":{"timestamp":" 947478297519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478297801","data":{"timestamp":" 947478297801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478305401","data":{"timestamp":" 947478305401"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAMPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478306707","data":{"timestamp":" 947478306707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478306719","data":{"timestamp":" 947478306719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478307822","data":{"timestamp":" 947478307822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WETU"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478307927","data":{"timestamp":" 947478307927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478309624","data":{"timestamp":" 947478309623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478311281","data":{"timestamp":" 947478311280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEFAHAMU"," userResponse":" UMEFAHAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478311597","data":{"timestamp":" 947478311597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478312177","data":{"timestamp":" 947478312176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478313337","data":{"timestamp":" 947478313337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAMPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478313844","data":{"timestamp":" 947478313843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478313865","data":{"timestamp":" 947478313865"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478314325","data":{"timestamp":" 947478314324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WETU"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478315065","data":{"timestamp":" 947478315064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478317766","data":{"timestamp":" 947478317765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478317900","data":{"timestamp":" 947478317899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" a17a187f-bd31-431e-9563-cb721a9e7a0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478331726","data":{"timestamp":" 947478331725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 0296717e-0b6b-4f99-9cb3-de416c8851d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" MKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478342839","data":{"timestamp":" 947478342839"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 0296717e-0b6b-4f99-9cb3-de416c8851d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478344455","data":{"timestamp":" 947478344454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 0296717e-0b6b-4f99-9cb3-de416c8851d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shangazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478347711","data":{"timestamp":" 947478347711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 0296717e-0b6b-4f99-9cb3-de416c8851d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shangazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" START_SHANGAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478349370","data":{"timestamp":" 947478349369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 0296717e-0b6b-4f99-9cb3-de416c8851d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shangazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478350995","data":{"timestamp":" 947478350994"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 0296717e-0b6b-4f99-9cb3-de416c8851d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAFUNZI"," userResponse":" MWANAFUNZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478354579","data":{"timestamp":" 947478354579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 0296717e-0b6b-4f99-9cb3-de416c8851d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAFUNZI"," userResponse":" MWANAFUNZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478356183","data":{"timestamp":" 947478356182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 0296717e-0b6b-4f99-9cb3-de416c8851d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478359141","data":{"timestamp":" 947478359141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 0296717e-0b6b-4f99-9cb3-de416c8851d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478360706","data":{"timestamp":" 947478360706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 0296717e-0b6b-4f99-9cb3-de416c8851d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478364617","data":{"timestamp":" 947478364616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 0296717e-0b6b-4f99-9cb3-de416c8851d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478366202","data":{"timestamp":" 947478366200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 0296717e-0b6b-4f99-9cb3-de416c8851d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478368686","data":{"timestamp":" 947478368686"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 0296717e-0b6b-4f99-9cb3-de416c8851d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478370286","data":{"timestamp":" 947478370285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 0296717e-0b6b-4f99-9cb3-de416c8851d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478373792","data":{"timestamp":" 947478373791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 0296717e-0b6b-4f99-9cb3-de416c8851d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478375432","data":{"timestamp":" 947478375431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 0296717e-0b6b-4f99-9cb3-de416c8851d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" babu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABU"," userResponse":" BABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478383384","data":{"timestamp":" 947478383384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 0296717e-0b6b-4f99-9cb3-de416c8851d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" babu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABU"," userResponse":" BABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478385065","data":{"timestamp":" 947478385064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 0296717e-0b6b-4f99-9cb3-de416c8851d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947478398486","data":{"timestamp":" 947478398486"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061547"," gameId":" 0296717e-0b6b-4f99-9cb3-de416c8851d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}